(Howard:)The application in your hand.
Give it to her.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(DMV Lady(to the person ahead of Sheldon in the queue):)Take this to the testing area.
Name at the top.
(DMV Lady(to the person ahead of Sheldon in the queue):)Sign the bottom, answer the questions,
bring it back. Next.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, but I have some concerns
about these questions.
(DMV Lady:)Look at that sign up there.
- Yes?
- Does it say, "I give a damn"?
(Leonard:)- No.
- That's because I don't.
(Sheldon:)Just look.
See, this first question makes no sense.
Look, "How many car lengths should you
leave in front of you when driving?"
(Sheldon:)There's no possible way to answer that.
(Sheldon:)A car length is not
a standardized unit of measure.
(DMV Lady:)Look at the sign.
- Sheldon, it's C. Just put down C.
- I don't need your help, Penny.
- Listen to that little girl, honey. Put C. Next.
SHELDON: No, no.
(Sheldon:)Wait, no, hang on.
Take a look at this next question.
(Scene:)Sheldon,
why are you arguing with the DMV?
(Sheldon:)How else are they going to learn?